<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:googleplay="https://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/play-podcasts.xsd" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:podcast="https://podcastindex.org/namespace/1.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AP Archive</title>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</link>
    <description>(28 Jan 2022) Divers, veterinarians and the coast guard were mounting a rescue operation Friday to help a whale calf that had become trapped in shallow water in a seaside area of the Greek capital.&#13;
The animal was an injured young Cuvier’s beaked whale, or Ziphius cavirostris, according to Arion, a research organization that provides veterinary care for stranded cetaceans. &#13;
The species usually inhabits deep waters, and it was unclear how it had been injured and why it became stranded in the Alimos area of southern Athens. &#13;
On Thursday, the whale had been sighted in shallow water in the nearby area of Vouliagmeni, and divers had been called in to lead it out to sea. &#13;
The operation had initially appeared successful, but the animal returned to shallow waters Friday morning.&#13;
“The prognosis unfortunately isn’t good,” said Environment and Energy Deputy Minister Giorgos Amyras, who was at the scene. &#13;
“The fact that it has been in these shallow waters for so many hours doesn’t give us much hope. But we of course are doing everything possible to save the animal,” he added. &#13;
He said two specialized veterinarians, a specialized veterinary nurse and four aid organizations had been brought in to try to save the whale.&#13;
A blood sample had been drawn and sent for analysis to determine what medication the animal might need, while an antibiotic had already been administered, Amyras said.&#13;
&#13;
Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork &#13;
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive &#13;
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​&#13;
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/ed395412adff4c698231f4291bef289c</description>
    <language>None</language>
    <category>News &amp; Politics</category>
    <generator>utipod</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.ytimg.com/vi_webp/4f2AtMFKOfY/maxresdefault.webp</url>
      <title>AP Archive</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Germany has a coronavirus wave powered by the omicron variant under control despite a string of new infection records, the health minister said Friday.
Cases as a result of the highly contagious variant in the European Union's most populous nation shot up at a later stage than in several other countries in the region. 
Officials attribute that to restrictions such as curbs on private gatherings, nightclub closures and requirements for restaurant and bar patrons to have received a booster shot or to present a negative test. 
Yet infections continue to rise steeply in the country of 83 million. 
On Thursday, new cases reported in the previous 24 hours topped 200,000 for the first time. 
On Friday, the infection rate reached another record of 1,073 new cases per 100,000 residents in a week.
Those numbers didn't deter Health Minister Karl Lauterbach from declaring that authorities “have the omicron wave in Germany well under control at the moment.”
Lauterbach told reporters in Berlin that the infection rate among the elderly - many of whom remain unvaccinated - is much lower than the average.
The omicron variant surge is so far slightly below projections, Lauterbach said. 
Daily infections are expected to reach up to 400,000 before falling, likely in mid-February. 
The drop could come later the same month because of a mutation of omicron known as BA.2, he added.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/c691948eda1f4705a17994e7e2a3f72a]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[German govt says omicron wave 'under control']]></title>
      <guid>3cyiN_CBVR0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3cyiN_CBVR0</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/3cyiN_CBVR0.mkv" length="5344662" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3cyiN_CBVR0/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Divers, veterinarians and the coast guard were mounting a rescue operation Friday to help a whale calf that had become trapped in shallow water in a seaside area of the Greek capital.
The animal was an injured young Cuvier’s beaked whale, or Ziphius cavirostris, according to Arion, a research organization that provides veterinary care for stranded cetaceans. 
The species usually inhabits deep waters, and it was unclear how it had been injured and why it became stranded in the Alimos area of southern Athens. 
On Thursday, the whale had been sighted in shallow water in the nearby area of Vouliagmeni, and divers had been called in to lead it out to sea. 
The operation had initially appeared successful, but the animal returned to shallow waters Friday morning.
“The prognosis unfortunately isn’t good,” said Environment and Energy Deputy Minister Giorgos Amyras, who was at the scene. 
“The fact that it has been in these shallow waters for so many hours doesn’t give us much hope. But we of course are doing everything possible to save the animal,” he added. 
He said two specialized veterinarians, a specialized veterinary nurse and four aid organizations had been brought in to try to save the whale.
A blood sample had been drawn and sent for analysis to determine what medication the animal might need, while an antibiotic had already been administered, Amyras said.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/ed395412adff4c698231f4291bef289c]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Rescue mission to help stranded whale in Greece]]></title>
      <guid>4f2AtMFKOfY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4f2AtMFKOfY</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/4f2AtMFKOfY.mkv" length="6585049" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4f2AtMFKOfY/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR SOCIAL READY VERSION WITHOUT CAPTIONS SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363444

FOR CUSTOMER READY VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363447

FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363424

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/cf8c1ba566a6467a9539c87775c84025]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[CAPTIONED 'The Afterparty' stars describe the best real life bashes they've been to]]></title>
      <guid>DARPcVXRnTc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DARPcVXRnTc</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/DARPcVXRnTc.mkv" length="3304052" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DARPcVXRnTc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) The head of a US Congressional delegation to Kyiv claimed on Friday that Russian President Vladimir Putin had united his adversaries amid the threat of conflict in Ukraine.
He's united the EU, he's united the NATO members, he's united the Ukrainian people and he's united the United States Congress, said Gregory Meeks.
The representatives, headed by Meeks, are on a visit to Kyiv to meet with senior Ukrainian officials, including President Volodymyr Zelenskyy.
While there are no plans and no desires for American boots on the ground here, we must do all that we can short of that to help the Ukrainians, said Republican Mark Green.
Democrat Tom Malinowski added that the sanctions that we have prepared will be absolutely devastating and they will be imposed should he (Vladimir Putin) move, and he knows it.
Russia said Friday it will not start a war in Ukraine but warned that the US and NATO have ignored its demands and left little room for compromise in the crisis.
Putin told French President Emmanuel Macron the West has failed to consider Russia’s key conditions of halting further NATO expansion, stopping the deployment of alliance weapons near Russian borders, and rolling back its forces from Eastern Europe, the Kremlin said.
The US and NATO formally rejected those demands this week, although Washington outlined areas where discussions are possible, offering hope that there could be a way to avoid war amid the buildup of more than 100,000 Russian troops near Ukraine.
Russia has repeatedly denied having any plans to invade its neighbor.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/05614d14fdd249c88bebdd7d9ec923f5]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[US congressional delegation visits Ukraine]]></title>
      <guid>_FOwtUblliw</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_FOwtUblliw</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/_FOwtUblliw.mkv" length="4217703" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_FOwtUblliw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) As of Friday, customers eating inside bars and restaurants and going to fitness centres in the city of Barcelona are no longer required to present COVID-19 passports upon entrance.  
Another restriction no longer in place is the limit of up to ten people during private gatherings.  
But nightlife businesses will remain closed until further notice, regional authorities said Tuesday. 
With one of Europe's highest vaccination rates, the Spanish government is laying the groundwork to treat the next infection surge not as an emergency but an illness that is here to stay.  
The idea is to move from crisis mode to control mode, approaching the virus in much the same way countries deal with flu or measles.   
That means accepting that infections will occur and providing extra care for at-risk people and patients with complications.  
A spike in new daily infections in December due to the omicron variant forced regional Catalan authorities to reinstate a night curfew during the Christmas holidays.   
The curfew was extended a further two weeks but lifted January 21.  
Other restrictions remain in place, such as wearing face masks outdoors.   
Officials credited the draconian measures with preventing a full collapse of the health system.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/35414c46048b43fda4bc919ffba6b25e]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Spain eases some coronavirus restrictions]]></title>
      <guid>_pLuuoCEfOs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_pLuuoCEfOs</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/_pLuuoCEfOs.mkv" length="7247094" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_pLuuoCEfOs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) 
RESTRICTION SUMMARY:
STORYLINE:
ASSOCIATED PRESS
Donetsk, Ucrania - 27 de enero de 2022
A medida que crece la tensión en la frontera entre Ucrania y Rusia, los residentes de un pueblo en las afueras de Donetsk esperan la paz.
Spartak, que todavía alberga a unas 80 familias, está cerca del frente del lado rebelde.
La mayoría de sus habitantes son personas mayores que rara vez salen a la calle, por temor a la amenaza de bombardeos.
SOUNDBITE (Ruso) - Valentina Pleshkovam, residente:
Solo esperamos que Rusia nos tome de una vez, porque esto tiene que detenerse en algún momento, dijo esta residente.
La tensión se ha disparado en las últimas semanas.
Estados Unidos y sus aliados de la OTAN temen un ataque de Moscú al ex estado soviético, por las tropas rusas desplegadas cerca de la frontera.
Rusia ha negado planes de invasión. 
SOUNDBITE (Ruso) - Irina (no dio apellido), residente:
Lo que está pasando ahora es no una guerra, es un fratricidio. Nosotros y Ucrania somos lo mismo, hemos sido lo mismo, dijo esta residente.
Mientras Moscú y Occidente evalúan sus próximos pasos, la OTAN dijo que estaba reforzando su disuasión en la región del Mar Báltico, y Estados Unidos ordenó a 8.500 soldados en alerta máxima.
Rusia ha lanzado una serie de ejercicios militares en el suroeste de su país, en Kaliningrado, en el Mar Báltico y en el Mar Negro y el Ártico.
Sus tropas también se dirigieron a Bielorrusia, lo que aumentó los temores de Occidente de que Moscú pudiera organizar un ataque contra Ucrania desde el norte.
Yesica Brumec, Associated Press
===========================================================
Clients are reminded: 
(i) to check the terms of their licence agreements for use of content outside news programming and that further advice and assistance can be obtained from the AP Archive on: Tel +44 (0) 20 7482 7482 Email: info@aparchive.com
(ii) they should check with the applicable collecting society in their Territory regarding the clearance of any sound recording or performance included within the AP Television News service 
(iii) they have editorial responsibility for the use of all and any content included within the AP Television News service and for libel, privacy, compliance and third party rights applicable to their Territory.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/1fcdfd90ddb443e0a1c81200ae5de014]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Aldeanos ucranianos tienen esperanza de paz en conflicto con Rusia]]></title>
      <guid>g8Xhm7Czz30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g8Xhm7Czz30</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/g8Xhm7Czz30.mkv" length="4073615" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/g8Xhm7Czz30/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363392

With its opening ceremony now just a week away, China has been using the Beijing Winter Olympics to promote winter sports, many of which are new to most Chinese, for fitness and business opportunities. 
The push has proved lifechanging for Li Wei. 
The tall, tanned 36-year-old farmer-turned ski coach works December to March at a resort in the Yanqing district, which will host skiing, luge and other sliding events for the Beijing Games.
Skiing boosted my income to another level, said Li, who charges 400 to 500 yuan ($60 to $80) per lesson — almost as much as his family earns in a week growing corn during warmer months. 
Many in Beijing have long enjoyed winter ice skating on canals and lakes. But now, young Chinese are expanding their aspirations from basketball, football and gymnastics to sports such as hockey and skiing.
The government and private companies have built ice rinks and ski runs. 
Public schools are adding skating and other winter sports. Parents are opening their wallets to pay for hockey teams and skating lessons. Villages near ski slopes are building inns to serve well-heeled tourists.
Wu Mengkai, 11, said hockey has turned him to being more extroverted and a very sunny person.
You can't be introverted when you play ice hockey, Wu said. You have to be brave enough to fight.
The Chinese capital has tightened anti-virus measures and ordered mass testing of some 2 million people in one district following outbreaks. Some families are barred from leaving their homes.
The Winter Games will take place without foreign tourists or ordinary spectators under China's zero tolerance strategy that aims to keep the virus out of the country. Athletes, reporters and officials are required to stay within areas that isolate them from general public.
Foreign sports brands see growth opportunities in China but are frustrated that marketing and business development are hampered by the anti-virus controls and ban on most foreigners from entering China.
That's kind of put a damper on things, said Jeffrey Potter, president of Proskatecorner Pte. Ltd., the China distributor of American hockey equipment maker True. 
If not for the virus, the marketing boost from the Olympics would have been bigger, really helping the economy and making hockey more popular, Potter said.
Despite the Games being off limits to ordinary spectators because of the pandemic, enthusiasm for winter sports remain high.
I want to be an ice hockey player in the future, said eight-year-old Guo Yuchen, who took up the sport at four and trains seven hours a week at a rink in Beijing. Then I can bring glory to my country.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/738ae9fb6d344cea8f0416b37957c75f]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Olympics give winter sports boost in China]]></title>
      <guid>v9pDwQSWndM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v9pDwQSWndM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/v9pDwQSWndM.mkv" length="4683846" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/v9pDwQSWndM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) The city of New York has given an emotional final salute to a rookie police officer gunned down with his partner a week ago. 
A funeral Mass for Jason Rivera was held Friday morning at St. Patrick's Cathedral. 
Mayor Eric Adams, who is a retired police captain, says he sees an echo of himself in the slain officer who had joined a department he had seen as flawed in hopes of improving it. 
The 22-year-old Rivera was recently married and barely into his second year on the force. 
He and Officer Wilbert Mora were fatally wounded when a gunman ambushed them in an apartment as they responded to a family dispute.
During the funeral service, New York City Police Commissioner Keechant Sewell posthumously promoted Rivera to the rank of Detective First Grade.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/f60469fa81e340cca66546fd28b0c797]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Emotional final salute to slain NYPD officer]]></title>
      <guid>zK2TeWC6eG8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zK2TeWC6eG8</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/zK2TeWC6eG8.mkv" length="11524539" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zK2TeWC6eG8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
