<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:googleplay="https://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0/play-podcasts.xsd" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:podcast="https://podcastindex.org/namespace/1.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>AP Archive</title>
    <link>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</link>
    <description>(28 Jan 2022) Divers, veterinarians and the coast guard were mounting a rescue operation Friday to help a whale calf that had become trapped in shallow water in a seaside area of the Greek capital.&#13;
The animal was an injured young Cuvier’s beaked whale, or Ziphius cavirostris, according to Arion, a research organization that provides veterinary care for stranded cetaceans. &#13;
The species usually inhabits deep waters, and it was unclear how it had been injured and why it became stranded in the Alimos area of southern Athens. &#13;
On Thursday, the whale had been sighted in shallow water in the nearby area of Vouliagmeni, and divers had been called in to lead it out to sea. &#13;
The operation had initially appeared successful, but the animal returned to shallow waters Friday morning.&#13;
“The prognosis unfortunately isn’t good,” said Environment and Energy Deputy Minister Giorgos Amyras, who was at the scene. &#13;
“The fact that it has been in these shallow waters for so many hours doesn’t give us much hope. But we of course are doing everything possible to save the animal,” he added. &#13;
He said two specialized veterinarians, a specialized veterinary nurse and four aid organizations had been brought in to try to save the whale.&#13;
A blood sample had been drawn and sent for analysis to determine what medication the animal might need, while an antibiotic had already been administered, Amyras said.&#13;
&#13;
Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork &#13;
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive &#13;
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​&#13;
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/ed395412adff4c698231f4291bef289c</description>
    <language>None</language>
    <category>News &amp; Politics</category>
    <generator>utipod</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://i.ytimg.com/vi_webp/4f2AtMFKOfY/maxresdefault.webp</url>
      <title>AP Archive</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363518, 4363536

The city of New York has given an emotional final salute to a rookie police officer gunned down with his partner a week ago. 
A funeral Mass for Jason Rivera was held Friday morning at St. Patrick's Cathedral. 
Mayor Eric Adams, who is a retired police captain, says he sees an echo of himself in the slain officer who had joined a department he had seen as flawed in hopes of improving it. 
The 22-year-old Rivera was recently married and barely into his second year on the force. 
He and Officer Wilbert Mora were fatally wounded when a gunman ambushed them in an apartment as they responded to a family dispute.
During the funeral service, New York City Police Commissioner Keechant Sewell posthumously promoted Rivera to the rank of Detective First Grade.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/a7431583e7e4431fa4856dd70da80dc9]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Emotional final salute to slain NYPD officer]]></title>
      <guid>-tewH_vDkVo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-tewH_vDkVo</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/-tewH_vDkVo.mkv" length="5750814" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi_webp/-tewH_vDkVo/sddefault.webp"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(31 Oct 1978) 10/31/78   w - 256 #9 
 new york, ny broadway by night. 

 fs new york - traffic ms night shot looking up at a coca cola sign & others & pan to otherss ms of traffic oming down broadway & theater signs in the bg & zoom into a policeman on horse back next to a parked police car ms & ls people walking on teh st & traffic going by. 
 (10/31/78 - 43ft) 

 new york - new york - (ss) night 
 ny - ny - streets - broadway 
 city traffic - ny - ny 
 police - ny - ny (ss) mounted 

 43 ft col orig

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/bebcaab405a1a5eb31d495c95f130694]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (bebcaab4-05a1-a5eb-31d4-95c95f130694)]]></title>
      <guid>0j1y_xH6Wko</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0j1y_xH6Wko</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/0j1y_xH6Wko.mkv" length="3305807" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0j1y_xH6Wko/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Thousands of people in the Democratic Republic of Congo have been displaced after they fled ongoing clashes between the Congolese army and M23 fighters this week. 
On Tuesday, a fresh attack carried out by the March 23 Movement, or M23 , targeted a Congolese army position in the territory of Rutshuru, just north of the city of Goma in eastern Congo. 
While authorities confirmed the attack, they did not provide any details about it. 
Eyewitnesses told The Associated Press that they saw gun fights and dead bodies. 
Since the beginning of this week, inhabitants from six villages in the country's east – including, Bukima, Nyesisi, and Ruhanga – have fled the violence. 
At least 2,000 people are now living in improvised shelters, in churches, schools or with host families. 
On Friday, the AP interviewed several eyewitnesses who fled to Kibumba and found shelter in a local church. 
Baseme Mashukano was a resident of Nyesisi, one of the six villages caught in the cross fire.
The attack began in Nyesisi, Ngungo, Kanombe. When we were in the field on Wednesday, we heard bullets over the hills and we fled. We abandoned everything and now we are here in Kibumba. We spend the night in the church while others sleep outside, we have nothing to eat, no food, no water or medicine, said Baseme. 
Another person displaced by the conflict, Sarah Kasigwa, says in the chaos she lost her three children and husband. 
We saw several dead people she said. We are sleeping here, in this school, on the ground. There is just cement, no blanket, we suffer a lot. 
32-year-old Tumaini Anouarite, a mother of five, said that she saw soldiers firing bullets in the nearby hills, and gunfights between the army and M23 fighters. 
On Friday, MONUSCO blue helmets were deployed in the area. 
The M23, which also calls itself the Revolutionary Army of Congo, is a former rebellion of Congolese backed by Rwanda and Uganda, which was defeated in 2013. 
Since November, the movement has been accused of being behind several attacks against the army. 
The attack took place in the vicinity of Virunga National Park, a UNESCO heritage site, renowned for its large gorilla population.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/9962e45292064dbc8ecfec33480fe129]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Thousands in DR Congo displaced after clashes]]></title>
      <guid>2qOSvcBdDdU</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2qOSvcBdDdU</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/2qOSvcBdDdU.mkv" length="10186287" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2qOSvcBdDdU/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR SOCIAL READY VERSION WITH CAPTIONS SEE STORY NUMBER:  4363445

FOR CUSTOMER READY VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363447

FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363424

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/986cc9f3bcd6419fbb95662e18016246]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA['The Afterparty' stars describe the best real life bashes they've been to]]></title>
      <guid>3XI3KueHb3E</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3XI3KueHb3E</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/3XI3KueHb3E.mkv" length="2789528" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3XI3KueHb3E/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Germany has a coronavirus wave powered by the omicron variant under control despite a string of new infection records, the health minister said Friday.
Cases as a result of the highly contagious variant in the European Union's most populous nation shot up at a later stage than in several other countries in the region. 
Officials attribute that to restrictions such as curbs on private gatherings, nightclub closures and requirements for restaurant and bar patrons to have received a booster shot or to present a negative test. 
Yet infections continue to rise steeply in the country of 83 million. 
On Thursday, new cases reported in the previous 24 hours topped 200,000 for the first time. 
On Friday, the infection rate reached another record of 1,073 new cases per 100,000 residents in a week.
Those numbers didn't deter Health Minister Karl Lauterbach from declaring that authorities “have the omicron wave in Germany well under control at the moment.”
Lauterbach told reporters in Berlin that the infection rate among the elderly - many of whom remain unvaccinated - is much lower than the average.
The omicron variant surge is so far slightly below projections, Lauterbach said. 
Daily infections are expected to reach up to 400,000 before falling, likely in mid-February. 
The drop could come later the same month because of a mutation of omicron known as BA.2, he added.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/c691948eda1f4705a17994e7e2a3f72a]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[German govt says omicron wave 'under control']]></title>
      <guid>3cyiN_CBVR0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3cyiN_CBVR0</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/3cyiN_CBVR0.mkv" length="5344662" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3cyiN_CBVR0/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) LEAD IN:   
The Iraqi army says it was reinforcing the country's border with Syria, building more fences and deploying additional troops to prevent the Islamic State militants from infiltrating the border.
The new measures come after IS militants launched a large operation last week at a prison in Syria's Hassakeh where the extremist group sought to break thousands of its fighters out of the detention facility.

STORY-LINE:  
The Iraqi army on Thursday said it was reinforcing the country's border with Syria after U.S.-backed Kurdish forces clashed in a weeklong battle with Islamic State militants at a prison in the nearby Syrian city of Hassakeh.
Iraqi Army commanders said they were building a third fence and deploying additional troops at the borderline to prevent IS militants from infiltrating the border area.
The new fence starts from Sinjar district in Nineveh province all the way down to Al Qaim in Anbar province.  
Maj. Gen. Jabbar Naima Karam, the commander of West Nineveh Operations, said all observation towers are equipped with supporting weapons, night visions, and infrared cameras that are connected to operation rooms at the Border Force Command base in Mosul.  
  
We reassure our people that our units are capable of protecting the border, he said.
Hassakeh, where IS launched a large operation to break thousands of its fighters out of the Gweiran prison in northeastern Syria, is about 50 km (30 miles) away from the Iraqi border.
The attack was the biggest by IS since the fall of the group's caliphate in 2019 and came as the militants staged a number of deadly attacks in Syria and Iraq that stoked fears they may be staging a comeback.  
  
Chief of Staff of the Iraqi Army Lt. Gen. Abdul-Amir Rasheed Yar Allah assured the Iraqi people that the assault in the nearby Syrian city won't affect the border.
Our message to all of our people is that things are good on the Iraqi-Syrian borders. What is happening in Hassakeh did not have a big impact on our territories so far. 
The Islamic State group's territorial control in Iraq and Syria was crushed by a years-long U.S.-backed campaign, but some fighters remained at large in sleeper cells that have killed scores of Iraqis and Syrians over the past months.  
Iraq shares a 599-kilometer (372-mile) border with Syria.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/32f2ba5e21b84c5ea2208889fad2d8a6]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Iraq reinforces Syrian border after IS attacks]]></title>
      <guid>4KkQ2skJNJM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4KkQ2skJNJM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/4KkQ2skJNJM.mkv" length="6734883" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4KkQ2skJNJM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Hundreds of hard-line worshippers in Tehran demonstrated after Friday prayers in support of the Iranian-backed Houthis and to condemn the killing of Yemenis by the Saudi-led coalition.
Protesters carried Yemeni flags and chanted slogans against Saudi Arabia and the United States as its ally. 
They called Saudis Wahhabi hypocrites who they said killed Shiites and children in Yemen. 
Demonstrators marched on the streets near Tehran's great Musalla Prayer Ground, while some members of the Houthi rebels distributed pictures of Yemeni victims. 
The protest came after the escalation of an offensive by the Saudi-led coalition on Houthi rebels, who are referred to as Ansarallah Movement by Tehran. 
A Saudi-led coalition airstrike hit a prison run by Yemen's Houthi rebels last Friday, killing at least 70 detainees and wounding dozens, a rebel minister said.  
The strike was part of a pounding aerial offensive that knocked the Arab world's poorest country off the internet. 
The intense campaign came after the Iran-backed Houthis claimed a drone and missile attack that struck inside the United Arab Emirates' capital earlier in the week - a major escalation in the conflict in Yemen where the Saudi-led coalition, with the UAE as a member, has battled the rebels since 2015. 
Taha al-Motawakel, Health Minister in the Houthi government which controls northern Yemen, said 70 detainees were killed at the prison and that he expected the number to rise as many others were seriously wounded.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/57e41d7d79514a558a0256904579e73b]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Hundreds in Tehran hold pro-Houthi rally]]></title>
      <guid>4R1h-ZMYaYI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4R1h-ZMYaYI</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/4R1h-ZMYaYI.mkv" length="5546766" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4R1h-ZMYaYI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) PRINCE ANDREW GIVES UP MEMBERSHIP OF PRESTIGIOUS GOLF CLUB
Britain's Prince Andrew has given up his honorary membership of the Royal and Ancient Golf Club of St. Andrews, one of the world's most prestigious golf clubs, as he fights allegations of sexual abuse that have forced him to retreat from public life.
The club in St. Andrews, Scotland, announced the move Friday (28 JANUARY 2022), two weeks after Andrew was stripped of his honorary military titles and roles with charitable organizations amid a U.S. civil lawsuit filed by a woman who says she was forced to have sex with Andrew when she was 17.
``I can confirm that the Royal and Ancient Golf Club of St. Andrews has received notification that the Duke of York will relinquish his honorary membership,'' the club said in a statement. ``We respect and appreciate his decision.''
Andrew, also known as the Duke of York, denies the allegations and has asked for a jury trial in the case filed in federal court in New York.
The decision to remove Andrew's military titles and charity positions was taken with the ``approval and agreement'' of his mother, Queen Elizabeth II, Buckingham Palace said in a statement Jan. 13. The prince stopped performing royal duties two years ago, after a disastrous BBC interview that stoked criticism about his relationship with the convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein.
The Duke of York will continue not to undertake any public duties and is defending this case as a private citizen,'' the palace said earlier this month.
The Royal and Ancient Golf Club of St. Andrews was founded in 1754 and helped administer the rules of golf for 250 years until that role was handed over to another organization. It remains a private golf club with about 2,400 members worldwide.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/8f344cc54f104ceaa8b52d13230d6944]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Prince Andrew gives up membership of prestigious golf club]]></title>
      <guid>4R6frq_fVGc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4R6frq_fVGc</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/4R6frq_fVGc.mkv" length="4806472" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4R6frq_fVGc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Divers, veterinarians and the coast guard were mounting a rescue operation Friday to help a whale calf that had become trapped in shallow water in a seaside area of the Greek capital.
The animal was an injured young Cuvier’s beaked whale, or Ziphius cavirostris, according to Arion, a research organization that provides veterinary care for stranded cetaceans. 
The species usually inhabits deep waters, and it was unclear how it had been injured and why it became stranded in the Alimos area of southern Athens. 
On Thursday, the whale had been sighted in shallow water in the nearby area of Vouliagmeni, and divers had been called in to lead it out to sea. 
The operation had initially appeared successful, but the animal returned to shallow waters Friday morning.
“The prognosis unfortunately isn’t good,” said Environment and Energy Deputy Minister Giorgos Amyras, who was at the scene. 
“The fact that it has been in these shallow waters for so many hours doesn’t give us much hope. But we of course are doing everything possible to save the animal,” he added. 
He said two specialized veterinarians, a specialized veterinary nurse and four aid organizations had been brought in to try to save the whale.
A blood sample had been drawn and sent for analysis to determine what medication the animal might need, while an antibiotic had already been administered, Amyras said.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/ed395412adff4c698231f4291bef289c]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Rescue mission to help stranded whale in Greece]]></title>
      <guid>4f2AtMFKOfY</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4f2AtMFKOfY</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/4f2AtMFKOfY.mkv" length="6585049" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4f2AtMFKOfY/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(27 Dec 1972) 12/27/72   c0030976 / color 
 new york:  new york weather: 

 spl cut story ny weather shows:  6 scenes people on 5th avenue: var shots of kids ice skating in central park: 
 (shot recently 156ft) 

 ny, ny - streets - fifth ave 
 skating - gen 
 parks - ny, ny - central 

 xx / 156 ft / 16 col / pos / d26386

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/fcfd76f9adfb0de113a4565a110045bb]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (fcfd76f9-adfb-0de1-13a4-565a110045bb)]]></title>
      <guid>7PNldhsdZJ8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7PNldhsdZJ8</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/7PNldhsdZJ8.mkv" length="9794456" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/7PNldhsdZJ8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR SOCIAL READY VERSION WITHOUT CAPTIONS SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363506

FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363462

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/b4b8e62d831148a3b5505c115b1acfc2]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[CAPTIONED will.i.am. welcomes new singer J. Rey Soul to Black Eyed Peas]]></title>
      <guid>C2t1Mltd0sA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C2t1Mltd0sA</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/C2t1Mltd0sA.mkv" length="1594985" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/C2t1Mltd0sA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR SOCIAL READY VERSION WITHOUT CAPTIONS SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363444

FOR CUSTOMER READY VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363447

FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363424

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/cf8c1ba566a6467a9539c87775c84025]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[CAPTIONED 'The Afterparty' stars describe the best real life bashes they've been to]]></title>
      <guid>DARPcVXRnTc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DARPcVXRnTc</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/DARPcVXRnTc.mkv" length="3304052" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DARPcVXRnTc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) A two-lane bridge collapsed in Pittsburgh, early Friday just hours before President Joe Biden was to visit the city to press for his $1 trillion infrastructure bill, which includes bridge maintenance. 
Authorities say there were minor injuries from the collapse but no fatalities. 
Police reported the span, on Forbes Avenue over Fern Hollow Creek in Frick Park, came down just before 7 a.m.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/a2e5548c303f4f098d50605f155d0172]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[PA bridge collapses ahead of Biden visit]]></title>
      <guid>FGuCnSkDPeo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FGuCnSkDPeo</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/FGuCnSkDPeo.mkv" length="1211150" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FGuCnSkDPeo/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(31 Aug 1971) 08/31/71   c0025984 / color 
 new york:  new york floods: 

 wnew ret ny floods shows:  shot of car thru flooded street:  mcu taxi thru water:  night shot broadway:  headline from allied chemical bldg telling about flood:  shot traffic down wet street:  people walking with umbrellas:  mcu feet walking on wet pavement:  mcu rain drops hitting puddle of water:  shot of bus thru flooded street:  shot of post office truck thru flooded street:  another shot bus thru flooded water:  mcu car thru water: 
 (shot recently 150ft) 

 rain (ss) 
 ny, ny - times square (area in rain) 
 umbrellas 
 weather - ny, ny 
 feet walking (in rain) 

 xx / 150 ft / 16 col / pos / r35633

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/7ace98af341266d406040f6c2efeb3bd]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (7ace98af-3412-66d4-0604-0f6c2efeb3bd)]]></title>
      <guid>Hnz5w8JruEU</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hnz5w8JruEU</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/Hnz5w8JruEU.mkv" length="9097062" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Hnz5w8JruEU/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) 
RESTRICTION SUMMARY: PART MUST CREDIT NOAA, DO NOT OBSCURE PERMIT NUMBER 
++MUSIC CLEARED FOR USE++
NOAA – MUST CREDIT
Off Maui, Hawaii – 26 January 2022
++QUALITY AS INCOMING++
1. Rescue crew attaches line to gear entangling whale
HEADLINE: Young humpback whale freed from entangled gear
2. Rescue crew grapples gear entangling whale  
ANNOTATION: A rescue team cut off about 140 feet of line and a plastic trawling buoy to free a young humpback whale off Maui on Wednesday. 
3. Rescue crew pulls up behind whale
ANNOTATION: Officials said the whale was in good condition but that the line wrapped around its tail had begun to cut into the animal's flesh.
4. Rescue crew frees whale from entangled gear ++MUTE++
ANNOTATION: The gear will be analyzed to determine its exact source. 
STORYLINE:
Federal officials say a yearling humpback whale off Hawaii has been freed from a life-threatening entanglement in mooring gear.
The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration said a rescue team cut off about 140 feet (43 meters) of line and a plastic trawling buoy when they freed the whale off Maui on Wednesday. 
The whale's tail and fins were wrapped in small-gauge line with the plastic buoy floating behind, the agency said in a statement. 
Officials said the whale was in good condition but that the line wrapped around its tail had begun to cut into the animal's flesh. The gear was of considerable weight, the agency said. 
The gear will be analyzed to determine its exact source. 
The animal's behavior was very evasive, and while it stayed near the surface, it maintained unusually rapid speeds, at times in excess of six knots, the agency said in a statement Thursday. 
Trained responders cut the gear off with a blade attached to a pole after getting close on an inflatable boat. It is a federal crime to approach a humpback whale and the team was working under under federal permit. 
Another humpback whale was spotted off Hawaii entangled in debris earlier this month.
===========================================================
Clients are reminded: 
(i) to check the terms of their licence agreements for use of content outside news programming and that further advice and assistance can be obtained from the AP Archive on: Tel +44 (0) 20 7482 7482 Email: info@aparchive.com
(ii) they should check with the applicable collecting society in their Territory regarding the clearance of any sound recording or performance included within the AP Television News service 
(iii) they have editorial responsibility for the use of all and any content included within the AP Television News service and for libel, privacy, compliance and third party rights applicable to their Territory.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/01b192dd0e624b8d97b632c5e63da650]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Young humpback whale freed from entangled gear]]></title>
      <guid>IQhfT4AVq3M</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IQhfT4AVq3M</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/IQhfT4AVq3M.mkv" length="3600129" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/IQhfT4AVq3M/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) A bridge spanning a ravine collapsed in Pittsburgh, requiring rescuers to rappel nearly 150 feet while others formed a human chain to help rescue multiple people from a bus. 
The collapse early Friday came hours before President Joe Biden was to visit the city to promote his $1 trillion infrastructure bill, which includes bridge maintenance. 
Authorities say there were minor injuries from the collapse but no fatalities. 
Police reported the span, on Forbes Avenue over Fern Hollow Creek in Frick Park, came down just before 7 a.m. 
A commuter bus fell along with the bridge when it collapsed.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/2597a27ada6a4cd0bfaf58756fce1ad5]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Overhead view of collapsed Pittsburgh bridge]]></title>
      <guid>KO78ZlH2NSc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KO78ZlH2NSc</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/KO78ZlH2NSc.mkv" length="2274490" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KO78ZlH2NSc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(19 Apr 1973) 05/09/73   c0033866 - color 
 new york:  mitchell eludes newsmen: 

 john mitchell shows:  various shots of building at 20 broad street, newsmen and photographers on vigil outside:  passer - by: 
 (shot 4/19/73 90ft) 

 mitchell, john - office 
 pol ethics (related) 

 90 ft / rev / uncut / story

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/b1848143796283a5537e126985f1fed3]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (b1848143-7962-83a5-537e-126985f1fed3)]]></title>
      <guid>NipmtEQbZAo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NipmtEQbZAo</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/NipmtEQbZAo.mkv" length="6452846" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NipmtEQbZAo/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) The first group of Ukrainian soldiers took part in military exercises Friday using anti-tank missile systems received from the UK. 
The training consisted of three days of theory and tactics practice followed by two days of practical exercises for the Next generation Light Anti-tank Weapon (NLAW).
Servicemen fired at targets at a distance of 300 to 600 metres from various positions.
The last stage of the drills took place in the International Centre for Peacekeeping and Security of the National Academy of Ukrainian Land Forces in the Lviv region. 
About 40 future NLAW instructors received certificates after the five-day course was over. 
They will be dispersed to military divisions to train new specialists.
According to the instructors, NLAWs can be operated by one person and their accuracy allows a user to hit the target in any weather. 
Russia's top diplomat said Friday that Moscow will not start a war in Ukraine but warned that it wouldn't allow the West to trample on its security interests, amid fears it is planning to invade its neighbor.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/edcd64a1d6fa485992dea0ac6e6a1272]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Ukrainians trained to use anti-tank missiles from UK]]></title>
      <guid>OLY_DJsa4lE</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OLY_DJsa4lE</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/OLY_DJsa4lE.mkv" length="7694445" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/OLY_DJsa4lE/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) President Joe Biden's commitment to nominating the U.S. Supreme Court's first Black female justice is an important step in addressing issues of gender, race and civil rights, legal experts say. 
Judith Browne Dianis, Executive Director of the Advancement Project, a racial justice organization, says that it is important to have a someone who has the lived experience of being a Black woman interpret constitutional law and make decision on the nation's highest court. 
Having a Back woman on the Supreme Court is exciting, the idea of it, because finally, we will not only have someone who will bring the experience of being Black in America, but someone who has lived at the intersections of race and gender. And hopefully will be a person who understands how race and gender have played in the law, she said. 
She said that while some have already criticized Biden's decision to appoint a Black female justice, she responds saying what is actually racist is that a Black woman has not sat on the Supreme Court since its inception. 
She also said that the current nomination is an opportunity for the legal profession to have more discussions about the term 'qualified.'
Dianis said the qualifications that have been used in the past are based on a career pathway that has been reserved for white men traditionally and some white women. T
There are very few people of color and Black people who have that pathway because there is a lot of discrimination that happens along the way, she said.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/e44fbacc3a454edfb68abeeb2a44be76]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Expert: SCOTUS pick a 'reckoning' for legal field]]></title>
      <guid>QbtBT9pjARA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QbtBT9pjARA</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/QbtBT9pjARA.mkv" length="10467004" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QbtBT9pjARA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363527

When Markicia Horton, 25, graduates this spring from the Texas Southern University's Thurgood Marshall School of Law in Houston and takes the bar, she'll be stepping into a world where a Black woman is set to be on the U.S. Supreme Court for the first time in its 232-year history.
With Stephen Breyer's retirement from the court and President Joe Biden's commitment to name a Black woman as his nominee, it is likely that as Horton moves into a profession, there will be a Black woman as a Supreme Court justice. What that means for her and thousands of other young women of color in law schools or serving as lawyers around the country is incalculable. 
But it comes as well, with concerns. According to the National Association for Law Placement, Black women made up 3.17 percent of associates at America's law firms in 2021 but less than 1 percent of partners. Women of color overall made up nearly 16 percent of associates at America's law firms but only about 4 percent of the partners.
I think that seeing the abortion cases presented before the Supreme Court and having another woman there essentially and having an African-American woman who can speak for the culture essentially as well as Americans as a whole, but just to give a different opinion, Horton says.
That, Horton said, is what a Black woman on the Supreme Court will bring to the table.
Her point of view at the Houston school is one shared more than 1,100 miles away at the North Carolina Central University School of Law where Professor Brenda Reddix-Smalls raised the issue during a Zoom session of the constitutional law course she teaches.
In North Carolina, examples of prominent Black female jurists include current state Supreme Court Justice Anita Earls, who has been suggested as someone Biden could consider for the vacancy created by Breyer, and former state Supreme Court Chief Justice Cheri Beasley, who is favored to win the Democratic nomination in the state's U.S. Senate race. Beasley was the first Black woman to oversee North Carolina's judicial branch. 
After the class ended, several students lingered to ask questions about assignments, and talk turned back to Biden's upcoming pick. Adaora Oguno, a 28-year old second-year student from Nashville, Tennessee, said that Biden's pick will fill a century's old vacancy that has left issues specific to Black women unaddressed.  
This is our moment, says Chazle' Woodley, student body president at North Carolina Central University School of Law. I'm excited, especially for the women who have been putting in work.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/96100193eda74e95bea9073920ecf562]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Black women law students: Justice pick 'our moment']]></title>
      <guid>RmezFCHIxFA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RmezFCHIxFA</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/RmezFCHIxFA.mkv" length="5599628" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RmezFCHIxFA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Through tears, the wife, Dominique Luzuriaga, of slain police officer Jason Rivera, 22, recalled the horror of seeing cellphone alerts about two officers being shot in Harlem. 
Her worries grew as she texted and called the former elementary school classmate she married this past October. 
She got no answer until the call that summoned her to a hospital where he was pronounced dead.
Luzuriaga made the comments while speaking Friday morning at her husband's funeral at St. Patrick's Cathedral.
Authorities are still investigating what motivated the gunman, who was shot by a third officer and later died.
Luzuriaga lashed out at new Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg, a Democrat who has instructed prosecutors not to pursue certain cases, including some allegations of resisting arrest.
The system continues to fail us. We are not safe anymore. Not even the members of the service, Luzuriaga said.
Bragg, who had no involvement with the officers' killer, responded in a statement that he was grieving and praying for the slain officers and will vigorously prosecute cases of violence against police.
Rivera was barely into his second year on the force. He and Officer Wilbert Mora were fatally wounded a week ago when a gunman ambushed them in an apartment as they responded to a family dispute.
Police filled the pews at St. Patrick's Cathedral Friday, and a sea of blue uniforms stretched for blocks as snow drifted outside the city's iconic church.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/2c0145ddbc9145a9ba05519a7707bb0d]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Killed officer's widow lashes out at Manhattan DA]]></title>
      <guid>SNHsXttomqM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SNHsXttomqM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/SNHsXttomqM.mkv" length="15086135" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SNHsXttomqM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) When Markicia Horton, 25, graduates this spring from the Texas Southern University's Thurgood Marshall School of Law in Houston and takes the bar, she'll be stepping into a world where a Black woman is set to be on the U.S. Supreme Court for the first time in its 232-year history.
With Stephen Breyer's retirement from the court and President Joe Biden's commitment to name a Black woman as his nominee, it is likely that as Horton moves into a profession, there will be a Black woman as a Supreme Court justice. What that means for her and thousands of other young women of color in law schools or serving as lawyers around the country is incalculable. 
But it comes as well, with concerns. According to the National Association for Law Placement, Black women made up 3.17 percent of associates at America's law firms in 2021 but less than 1 percent of partners. Women of color overall made up nearly 16 percent of associates at America's law firms but only about 4 percent of the partners.
I think that seeing the abortion cases presented before the Supreme Court and having another woman there essentially and having an African-American woman who can speak for the culture essentially as well as Americans as a whole, but just to give a different opinion, Horton says.
That, Horton said, is what a Black woman on the Supreme Court will bring to the table.
Her point of view at the Houston school is one shared more than 1,100 miles away at the North Carolina Central University School of Law where Professor Brenda Reddix-Smalls raised the issue during a Zoom session of the constitutional law course she teaches.
In North Carolina, examples of prominent Black female jurists include current state Supreme Court Justice Anita Earls, who has been suggested as someone Biden could consider for the vacancy created by Breyer, and former state Supreme Court Chief Justice Cheri Beasley, who is favored to win the Democratic nomination in the state's U.S. Senate race. Beasley was the first Black woman to oversee North Carolina's judicial branch. 
After the class ended, several students lingered to ask questions about assignments, and talk turned back to Biden's upcoming pick. Adaora Oguno, a 28-year old second-year student from Nashville, Tennessee, said that Biden's pick will fill a century's old vacancy that has left issues specific to Black women unaddressed.  
This is our moment, says Chazle' N. Woodley, student body president at North Carolina Central University School of Law. I'm excited, especially for the women who have been putting in the work.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/11731419bd2b472e860d50446b004831]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Black women law students:Justice pick 'our moment']]></title>
      <guid>SRM4dqSK8r4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SRM4dqSK8r4</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/SRM4dqSK8r4.mkv" length="4821343" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SRM4dqSK8r4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR SOCIAL READY VERSION WITH CAPTIONS SEE STORY NUMBER:  4363506

FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363462

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/da2a4b0b1a33484fbfda5d4e2fb7bf93]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[will.i.am. welcomes new singer J. Rey Soul to Black Eyed Peas]]></title>
      <guid>SoOd0KTVQUI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SoOd0KTVQUI</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/SoOd0KTVQUI.mkv" length="1559222" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SoOd0KTVQUI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(27 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363356

The White House insists President Joe Biden is looking forward to working with Republicans as he looks to nominate a replacement for retiring Supreme Court Justice Stephen Breyer, but press secretary Jen Psaki warned Republicans not to play games by pre-emptively criticizing a potential Supreme Court nominee before she is even selected.
We have not mentioned a single name. We have not put out a list. The president made it very clear he has not made a selection and there are, if anyone is saying they plan to characterize whoever he nominates after thorough consideration with both parties as 'radical' before they knew literally anything about who she is, they just obliterated their own credibility, Psaki said.
Her comments came after Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell said he hoped Biden would not “outsource this important decision to the radical left.” 
Our intention is to not play games. The president's intention is to consult with members of both parties, and his intention is to nominate a qualified candidate who after after completing a rigorous process, who is worthy of the excellence and decency of Breyer's legacy, Psaki added.
The press secretary also dismissed those who suggest Biden's pledge to name black woman to the Supreme Court is an example of affirmative action.
It's been over 230 years, as we know, since the Supreme Court came into being. A black woman has never served on it. And the president's view is that anyone who's saying that that's not possible or we can't find the most eminently qualified person, that's ludicrous, Psaki said. 
The fact that no black woman has been nominated shows a deficiency of the past election processes, not a lack of qualified candidates to be nominated to the Supreme Court, she added.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/89812a1b739d4998afe6b3bd50c3af54]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[WH warns GOP: Don't play games with SCOTUS nominee]]></title>
      <guid>WncZjSrXVmQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WncZjSrXVmQ</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/WncZjSrXVmQ.mkv" length="3593224" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WncZjSrXVmQ/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Six rockets struck Baghdad's international airport facility on Friday, damaging two commercial planes but causing no casualties, Iraq's military said in a statement. 
The rockets fired in the early morning landed on planes parked in a waiting area of Iraqi Airways, the country's national carrier, the statement said.
The military said launch pads for the missiles had been located in the nearby Abu Ghraib area. 
The airport contains an Iraqi military base that hosts U.S. and other coalition advisors.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/a3e6b52febcd48768109998673973075]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Rocket attack damages planes in Baghdad]]></title>
      <guid>XAkGfNhvXH4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XAkGfNhvXH4</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/XAkGfNhvXH4.mkv" length="1815337" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XAkGfNhvXH4/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Residents of Burkina Faso's capital Ouagadougou reacted on Friday to a speech given by their new military leader, Lt. Col. Paul Henri Sandaogo Damiba the night before. 
Damiba addressed the nation after mutinous soldiers forced democratically elected President Roch Marc Christian Kabore to resign this week, announcing they are now in charge of the West African country that's under siege by Islamic extremists.
The junta said Kabore failed to stem the jihadist violence that has killed thousands during his time in power. 
However, there are already new concerns that the coup could ultimately result in more attacks across Burkina Faso.
However, Young farmer Abdoul Aziz Compaore believed that if security comes back, it is up to us (Burkinabè) to see if we are going to make an electoral calendar or not.
That is to say, that if the elections are this year or next year, it is not a problem as long as the president does a good job, we can leave it, he explained.
Others welcomed the coup leader's promise of fighting terrorism and work to help thousands of internally displaced people go back to their homes. 
We hope that he succeeds in defeating terrorism and that everyone can return to their villages because when we see widows and orphans on the streets begging it is too sad, said hairdresser Kadi Ouedraogo. 
The international community has condemned the coup, despite widespread local support.  
On Friday the West African block ECOWAS, has decided to suspend Burkina Faso in the aftermath of this week's coup, making it the third nation in the regional bloc to be punished for a military takeover in only 18 months, following Mali and Guinea. 
In his first address to the nation since seizing power, Damiba said Thursday he was going to bring back security and order to the conflict-ridden nation, and unite the country. 
But he also warned that betrayal wouldn't be tolerated. 
Damiba, leader of the Patriotic Movement for Safeguarding and Restoration (MPSR), spoke from the presidential palace.
He explained that the country was facing an unprecedented crisis and the junta's priority would be to restore security by renewing the will to fight among its soldiers and by listening to people to form a path forward.  
Damiba also called on the international community not to turn its back on Burkina Faso.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/060a63281f344f6d9f68066e6708be28]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Burkinabe citizens react to coup leader's speech]]></title>
      <guid>_-4ZGZPSRPs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-4ZGZPSRPs</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/_-4ZGZPSRPs.mkv" length="8057463" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_-4ZGZPSRPs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) The head of a US Congressional delegation to Kyiv claimed on Friday that Russian President Vladimir Putin had united his adversaries amid the threat of conflict in Ukraine.
He's united the EU, he's united the NATO members, he's united the Ukrainian people and he's united the United States Congress, said Gregory Meeks.
The representatives, headed by Meeks, are on a visit to Kyiv to meet with senior Ukrainian officials, including President Volodymyr Zelenskyy.
While there are no plans and no desires for American boots on the ground here, we must do all that we can short of that to help the Ukrainians, said Republican Mark Green.
Democrat Tom Malinowski added that the sanctions that we have prepared will be absolutely devastating and they will be imposed should he (Vladimir Putin) move, and he knows it.
Russia said Friday it will not start a war in Ukraine but warned that the US and NATO have ignored its demands and left little room for compromise in the crisis.
Putin told French President Emmanuel Macron the West has failed to consider Russia’s key conditions of halting further NATO expansion, stopping the deployment of alliance weapons near Russian borders, and rolling back its forces from Eastern Europe, the Kremlin said.
The US and NATO formally rejected those demands this week, although Washington outlined areas where discussions are possible, offering hope that there could be a way to avoid war amid the buildup of more than 100,000 Russian troops near Ukraine.
Russia has repeatedly denied having any plans to invade its neighbor.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/05614d14fdd249c88bebdd7d9ec923f5]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[US congressional delegation visits Ukraine]]></title>
      <guid>_FOwtUblliw</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_FOwtUblliw</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/_FOwtUblliw.mkv" length="4217703" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_FOwtUblliw/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) As of Friday, customers eating inside bars and restaurants and going to fitness centres in the city of Barcelona are no longer required to present COVID-19 passports upon entrance.  
Another restriction no longer in place is the limit of up to ten people during private gatherings.  
But nightlife businesses will remain closed until further notice, regional authorities said Tuesday. 
With one of Europe's highest vaccination rates, the Spanish government is laying the groundwork to treat the next infection surge not as an emergency but an illness that is here to stay.  
The idea is to move from crisis mode to control mode, approaching the virus in much the same way countries deal with flu or measles.   
That means accepting that infections will occur and providing extra care for at-risk people and patients with complications.  
A spike in new daily infections in December due to the omicron variant forced regional Catalan authorities to reinstate a night curfew during the Christmas holidays.   
The curfew was extended a further two weeks but lifted January 21.  
Other restrictions remain in place, such as wearing face masks outdoors.   
Officials credited the draconian measures with preventing a full collapse of the health system.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/35414c46048b43fda4bc919ffba6b25e]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Spain eases some coronavirus restrictions]]></title>
      <guid>_pLuuoCEfOs</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_pLuuoCEfOs</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/_pLuuoCEfOs.mkv" length="7247094" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_pLuuoCEfOs/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Argentina has reached an agreement with the International Monetary Fund to refinance more than $40 billion in debt, President Alberto Fernández said Friday.
Speaking at a news conference after the announcement Argentina's Economic Minister laid out some of the details of the agreement.
Argentina was able to reach a policy agreement with the International Monetary Fund without there being adjustment policies, stated Martin Guzman.
The exchange rate policy is going to continue along the lines in which it has been carried out and we set an objective of accumulation of international reserves, which is very important to favor resilience on the external front, he said.
Since 2020, Argentina has been in an arduous negotiation with the IMF to refinance the debt contracted in 2018 during the government of conservative Mauricio Macri in the midst of a currency crisis.
Argentina had spent three years trying to renegotiate repayment terms with the IMF and considered a deal vital to stabilizing an economy whose lengthy crisis has been hit as well by the pandemic.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/ae1f184750f74f3e8164a783614569bb]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Argentina reaches debt refinance agreement with IMF]]></title>
      <guid>bT4Q0GnVRDo</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bT4Q0GnVRDo</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/bT4Q0GnVRDo.mkv" length="3876138" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bT4Q0GnVRDo/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363518, 4363536

Dominique Luzuriaga, the wife of slain NYPD police officer Jason Rivera, spoke at her husband's funeral on Friday. 
She lashed out at new Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg, a Democrat who has instructed prosecutors not to pursue certain cases, including some allegations of resisting arrest.
Rivera and Officer Wilbert Mora were fatally wounded a week ago when a gunman ambushed them in an apartment as they responded to a family dispute.
Bragg, who had no involvement with the officers' killer, responded in a statement that he was grieving and praying for the slain officers and will vigorously prosecute cases of violence against police.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/5eb3010dcb7442a187347432b8700ce3]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Killed officer's widow lashes out at Manhattan DA]]></title>
      <guid>bjtx4BPbugc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bjtx4BPbugc</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/bjtx4BPbugc.mkv" length="7200064" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bjtx4BPbugc/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) 
RESTRICTION SUMMARY:
STORYLINE:
ASSOCIATED PRESS
San Pablo - 27 de enero de 2022
La población sin hogar en la ciudad de San Pablo aumentó un 31 por ciento durante la pandemia de COVID-19, según datos de un nuevo censo.
Las autoridades registraron casi 32.000 personas viviendo en la calle. Cifra más elevada que la del resto de las ciudades del país.
Luiz Carlos da Silva fue uno de los que se quedó sin hogar durante la pandemia.
Desde septiembre del año pasado, duerme en una carpa improvisada en la acera con su esposa, embarazada de tres meses.
SOUNDBITE (Portugués) - Luiz Carlos da Silva, persona sin hogar:
Hasta el año pasado yo tenía una buena vida. Tenía mi casa, mis bienes, tenía todo, y mira dónde estoy ahora, dijo da Silva.
Otra familia sin un techo es la de Sheila Carvalho de Souza. Ella y sus cuatro hijos reciben donaciones de ropa y alimento de un residente local.
SOUNDBITE (Portugués) - Sheila Carvalho de Souza, persona sin hogar:
Hoy voy a comer carne porque recibí esta comida y hay mucha comida aquí, dijo de Souza, quien recoge artículos reciclables en las calles.
El censo se iba a realizar en 2023, pero el gobierno local lo adelantó debido a la escalada de pobreza agravada por la pandemia y la necesidad de generar proyectos para esta población.
Según el Instituto Brasileño de Geografía y Estadística, había 13,5 millones de personas desempleadas en el país en el tercer trimestre de 2021.
Yesica Brumec, Associated Press
===========================================================
Clients are reminded: 
(i) to check the terms of their licence agreements for use of content outside news programming and that further advice and assistance can be obtained from the AP Archive on: Tel +44 (0) 20 7482 7482 Email: info@aparchive.com
(ii) they should check with the applicable collecting society in their Territory regarding the clearance of any sound recording or performance included within the AP Television News service 
(iii) they have editorial responsibility for the use of all and any content included within the AP Television News service and for libel, privacy, compliance and third party rights applicable to their Territory.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/af9080f0da0640068eb7337efe874310]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Crece cantidad de personas sin hogar en San Pablo debido a la pandemia]]></title>
      <guid>bv6a42CCVLA</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bv6a42CCVLA</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/bv6a42CCVLA.mkv" length="3267549" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bv6a42CCVLA/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Nov 1977) 11/28/77    w - 37 #8 
 new york:  christmas shopping 

 fs xmas shopping shows:  shot of people down street: shot of santa claus standing by volunteers of america chimney outside on street:  ringing bell:  cu little boy in stroller wheeled down st:  another santa claus:   people walking along some wheeling children in strollers:  people going into & coming out of dept, store:  shots of people walking along ave:  shot another santa claus: 
 (shot 54ft) 

 christmas 
 stores - ny ny 
 santa claus 
 infants & toddlers 
 crowds - strollers 

 xx / 54 ft / 16 color / orig /

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/5f1b4778c7b572efe981d084863a43fe]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (5f1b4778-c7b5-72ef-e981-d084863a43fe)]]></title>
      <guid>coba80GJS28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=coba80GJS28</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/coba80GJS28.mkv" length="4469071" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/coba80GJS28/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) The town of Chebaa is used to snow in January but a recent storm, which has blanketed most of Lebanon, has left the town with snowfall the town hasn't been seen in a decade.
Snow trucks struggle to keep up with the amount of snow, leading many mountainous roads in Lebanon closed due to the weather.  
The roads are opening but that's not helping because the weather as you can see, a storm one right after the other. So the roads are staying closed so it has been hard to move around, said Mohammad Daher, a Chebaa resident.  
A winter storm has been battering the eastern Mediterranean, bringing heavy rains and wind to the Middle East this past week. 
Temperatures reached below 0 Celsius in some parts of the Middle East.
Lebanon, a country of 6 million people, is home to 1.5 million Syrian refugees and as Lebanon grapples with an unprecedented economic crisis, poverty has deepened the Lebanese people. 
Sky-rocketing fuel prices coupled with a currency collapse has meant many essential commodities, including fuel needed for heaters, are now out of reach for the average citizen.
For Dalal Moussa, the cold weather has isolated her in her home. 
A person can't even go outside to go get some fruits even. We can even check on each other. Nothing. There is no diesel. If someone has a little bit of diesel, he's using it lightly so that we can last the winter, she said. 
She turns off her heater at night to save on diesel and only stays warm in the coldest hours of the day with just blankets. 
And with no electricity, an electric heater is not a choice for many in Lebanon.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/230d0917e101491bbdced80a4c78dc13]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Snow in Lebanon as cold front intensifies]]></title>
      <guid>fG1qZnW2T8Y</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fG1qZnW2T8Y</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/fG1qZnW2T8Y.mkv" length="7321223" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fG1qZnW2T8Y/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Portugal on Friday ended two weeks of political campaigning for national elections, coming amidst an omicron surge in the country. 
On Friday leader of the Social Democrats, the main opposition party, Rui Rio gathered hundreds of supporters in downtown Lisbon as a show of confidence ahead of Sunday's vote.
In recent days, polls have brought the two running candidates closer, with speculation that either Rio and current Prime Minister and Socialist leader Antonio Costa could win. 
The country's facing a snap election for a new parliament and government follows a political crisis caused when the minority government formed by the Socialists in 2019 collapsed last November, halfway through its four-year term, when parliament rejected its 2022 state budget.
The spending plan is key. 
Portugal, a country of 10.3 million people, is poised to begin deploying some 45 billion euros ($50.8 billion) in help from the EU to help fire up the economy after the COVID-19 pandemic.
The new funds are seen as a chance for Portugal to make up lost economic ground.
But the snap election, intended to clarify the country's direction, could backfire and leave Portugal back where it started two months ago - with a vulnerable minority government.
An apparent surge in support for smaller parties means the two main parties will likely have to cut a deal with one or more of them, with an extended period of political negotiation expected.
The country's two main parties, the center-left Socialists and the center-right Social Democrats, have alternated in power for decades, but Portugal's problems have continued. 
  
Those two parties have for decades collected around 70% of the vote, alternating in government, and opinion polls suggest a close race between them this time.
  
Portugal's economy has been falling behind the rest of the EU since 2000, when its real annual GDP per capita was 16,230 euros ($18,300) compared with an EU average of 22,460 ($25,330).
By 2020, Portugal had edged higher to 17,070 euros ($19,250) while the bloc's average surged to 26,380 euros ($29,750).
  
Sunday's ballot is taking place amid a surge in cases blamed on the highly infectious omicron coronavirus variant, with hundreds of thousands of infected people confined at home. 
To reconcile the constitutional right to vote and the duty to care for public health, authorities are allowing infected people to go to polling stations, with a recommendation they go in a less busy evening time slot.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/0e4820fd39e84742b53c087bfa3d401b]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Main opposition final rally before Portugal election]]></title>
      <guid>g5JT-1ty34E</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g5JT-1ty34E</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/g5JT-1ty34E.mkv" length="9440538" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/g5JT-1ty34E/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) 
RESTRICTION SUMMARY:
STORYLINE:
ASSOCIATED PRESS
Donetsk, Ucrania - 27 de enero de 2022
A medida que crece la tensión en la frontera entre Ucrania y Rusia, los residentes de un pueblo en las afueras de Donetsk esperan la paz.
Spartak, que todavía alberga a unas 80 familias, está cerca del frente del lado rebelde.
La mayoría de sus habitantes son personas mayores que rara vez salen a la calle, por temor a la amenaza de bombardeos.
SOUNDBITE (Ruso) - Valentina Pleshkovam, residente:
Solo esperamos que Rusia nos tome de una vez, porque esto tiene que detenerse en algún momento, dijo esta residente.
La tensión se ha disparado en las últimas semanas.
Estados Unidos y sus aliados de la OTAN temen un ataque de Moscú al ex estado soviético, por las tropas rusas desplegadas cerca de la frontera.
Rusia ha negado planes de invasión. 
SOUNDBITE (Ruso) - Irina (no dio apellido), residente:
Lo que está pasando ahora es no una guerra, es un fratricidio. Nosotros y Ucrania somos lo mismo, hemos sido lo mismo, dijo esta residente.
Mientras Moscú y Occidente evalúan sus próximos pasos, la OTAN dijo que estaba reforzando su disuasión en la región del Mar Báltico, y Estados Unidos ordenó a 8.500 soldados en alerta máxima.
Rusia ha lanzado una serie de ejercicios militares en el suroeste de su país, en Kaliningrado, en el Mar Báltico y en el Mar Negro y el Ártico.
Sus tropas también se dirigieron a Bielorrusia, lo que aumentó los temores de Occidente de que Moscú pudiera organizar un ataque contra Ucrania desde el norte.
Yesica Brumec, Associated Press
===========================================================
Clients are reminded: 
(i) to check the terms of their licence agreements for use of content outside news programming and that further advice and assistance can be obtained from the AP Archive on: Tel +44 (0) 20 7482 7482 Email: info@aparchive.com
(ii) they should check with the applicable collecting society in their Territory regarding the clearance of any sound recording or performance included within the AP Television News service 
(iii) they have editorial responsibility for the use of all and any content included within the AP Television News service and for libel, privacy, compliance and third party rights applicable to their Territory.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/1fcdfd90ddb443e0a1c81200ae5de014]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Aldeanos ucranianos tienen esperanza de paz en conflicto con Rusia]]></title>
      <guid>g8Xhm7Czz30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g8Xhm7Czz30</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/g8Xhm7Czz30.mkv" length="4073615" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/g8Xhm7Czz30/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) 
RESTRICTION SUMMARY: PART MUST CREDIT NOAA, DO NOT OBSCURE PERMIT NUMBER
NOAA – MUST CREDIT; DO NOT OBSCURE PERMIT NUMBER
Off Maui, Hawaii – 26 January 2022
++QUALITY AS INCOMING++
1. Rescue crew attaches line to gear entangling whale
2. Rescue crew grapples gear entangling whale ++4X3 VIDEO AS INCOMING++
3. Various, rescue crew pulls up behind whale
4. Rescue crew frees whale from entangled gear ++MUTE++
STORYLINE:
Federal officials say a yearling humpback whale off Hawaii has been freed from a life-threatening entanglement in mooring gear.
The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration said a rescue team cut off about 140 feet (43 meters) of line and a plastic trawling buoy when they freed the whale off Maui on Wednesday. 
The whale's tail and fins were wrapped in small-gauge line with the plastic buoy floating behind, the agency said in a statement. 
Officials said the whale was in good condition but that the line wrapped around its tail had begun to cut into the animal's flesh. The gear was of considerable weight, the agency said. 
The gear will be analyzed to determine its exact source. 
The animal's behavior was very evasive, and while it stayed near the surface, it maintained unusually rapid speeds, at times in excess of six knots, the agency said in a statement Thursday. 
Trained responders cut the gear off with a blade attached to a pole after getting close on an inflatable boat. It is a federal crime to approach a humpback whale and the team was working under under federal permit. 
Another humpback whale was spotted of Hawaii earlier this month, also entangled in debris.
===========================================================
Clients are reminded: 
(i) to check the terms of their licence agreements for use of content outside news programming and that further advice and assistance can be obtained from the AP Archive on: Tel +44 (0) 20 7482 7482 Email: info@aparchive.com
(ii) they should check with the applicable collecting society in their Territory regarding the clearance of any sound recording or performance included within the AP Television News service 
(iii) they have editorial responsibility for the use of all and any content included within the AP Television News service and for libel, privacy, compliance and third party rights applicable to their Territory.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/21a316e73ef94ab3b1e34f8a466c946a]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Young humpback whale freed from entangled gear]]></title>
      <guid>gKVRMaTuZUQ</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gKVRMaTuZUQ</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/gKVRMaTuZUQ.mkv" length="5260247" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/gKVRMaTuZUQ/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(10 May 1972) 05/10/72   c0025922 / color 
 new york city:  anti - war demonstrators bring traffic to standstill in midtown manhattan: 

 nxc 45983 it & t demo shows:  (bg sof throughout) mc tilt down itt bldg to crowd of pickets at entrance:  cu little boy with sign blood is on congress hands a b52 bomber on his jacket:  cu crowd shot with signs, baby's on their backs:  ms simulated bombs dropping from window of bldg:  cu pan shot crowd:  cu pickets (play act) shoot - ing down viet cong & sound of bomb falling:  ms zoom in on demo stopping traffic:  cu cops make arrest:  cu woman with baby in crowd:  cu pan shot crowd with viet cong flags, zoom in on itt bldg: 
 (shot 5/10/72 70ft) 

 itt 
 svn - anti policy 
 flags - vietcong 

 xx / 70 ft / 16 col / pos / opt track 
 200 ft / 16 col / pos / cuts /

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/3c74c191bf54013eada93fb03f0bcc5d]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (3c74c191-bf54-013e-ada9-3fb03f0bcc5d)]]></title>
      <guid>iXt9C10xdBM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iXt9C10xdBM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/iXt9C10xdBM.mkv" length="5709290" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iXt9C10xdBM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Germany expressed regret Friday that Russia has announced the suspension of mutual military inspections at a time of heightened tensions between Moscow and NATO.
The inspections are intended as confidence-building measures among members of the Organizations for Security and Cooperation in Europe.
A spokesman for Germany's Foreign Ministry said Russia recently announced it would suspend the inspections until the end of February, citing the spread of the omicron variant.
Because of this an inspection on Russian territory in the border region of Ukraine, Belarus and Russia, which Latvia requested and Russia had previously agreed to, won't currently be possible, said the spokesman, Christofer Burger.
We expressly regret this step because particularly in the current situation anything which creates greater transparency would help reduce tensions, he said. That's why we are calling on Russia to voluntarily and extensively inform OSCE member states about its activities.
Burger said Russia had also unilaterally canceled inspections it was due to conduct in Germany.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/6f34c5e2f8a74278bfb103d1a661cb72]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Germany calls for more transparency from Russia]]></title>
      <guid>oahCFhNw-nI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oahCFhNw-nI</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/oahCFhNw-nI.mkv" length="1352639" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oahCFhNw-nI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(3 Mar 1973) 03/03/73   c0032599 - color 
 new york:  weather 

 various shots of traffic:  people walking umbrellas open: skating rink in rockefeller center:  street pedestrians: 
 (shot 3/3/73 100ft) 

 rain - ny - ny 
 umbrellas 
 skating - gen 
 crowds (ss) in rain 

 100 ft / col / rev / uncut

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/5749b37ceb50320dd5ad510e256518bb]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[News Item (5749b37c-eb50-320d-d5ad-510e256518bb)]]></title>
      <guid>ozocy1KT8lM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ozocy1KT8lM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/ozocy1KT8lM.mkv" length="6722566" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ozocy1KT8lM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363515

Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy on Friday sought to play down fears of a war between his country and Russia, saying in a news conference that he did not believe that the situation is worse now than it was in early 2021 when Russia began amassing troops on the border between the two nations.
 President Joe Biden on Thursday warned Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy that there is a distinct possibility that Russia could take military action against the former Soviet state in February. Russia has repeatedly denied having any such plans.
Zelenskyy, however, sought to play down the war fears, said on Friday that Western alarm over an imminent invasion has prompted many investors in the country's financial markets to cash out.
Meanwhile the head of a US Congressional delegation to Kyiv claimed on Friday that Russian President Vladimir Putin had united his adversaries amid the threat of conflict in Ukraine.
He's united the EU, he's united the NATO members, he's united the Ukrainian people and he's united the United States Congress, said Gregory Meeks.
The representatives, headed by Meeks, are on a visit to Kyiv to meet with senior Ukrainian officials, including President Volodymyr Zelenskyy.
While there are no plans and no desires for American boots on the ground here, we must do all that we can short of that to help the Ukrainians, said Republican Mark Green.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/4c5aaef7ed174d2db7897e38742ae10a]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Ukrainian president plays down war fears]]></title>
      <guid>rHkCDmJ4PrU</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rHkCDmJ4PrU</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/rHkCDmJ4PrU.mkv" length="3309837" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/rHkCDmJ4PrU/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) Novak Djokovic on Friday was flanked with honors at a small Adriatic Sea resort in Montenegro, as fresh doubt emerged over the timing of the positive COVID-19 test he used to enter Australia in an attempt to compete in the Australian Open.
The BBC reported on Friday that there are discrepancies in the numbers of his tests that were issued by the health authorities in Serbia with the numbers of other tests issued at the same time in the Balkan country.
Djokovic's media team and the Institute of Public Health in Serbia did not immediately respond to a request for comment from the Associated Press. Senior Serbian health officials have previously said that his test was valid and issued by a relevant institution.
Djokovic was deported from Australia and barred from playing in the Australian Open earlier this month after a 11-day visa saga on the eve of the tournament because he failed to meet Australia's strict COVID-19 vaccination requirements.
To enter Australia, Djokovic submitted a positive COVID-19 test issued in Serbia from Dec. 16 for a visa exemption on the grounds that he had contracted the disease prior to the tournament.
The 34-year-old player is not vaccinated and the Australian government decided to cancel his visa and deport Djokovic, saying his presence in Australia could stir anti-vaccination sentiments.
Djokovic has said he would make no public comments until the end of the Australia Open.
On Friday, several hundred people greeted Djokovic outside the municipal building in Budva as he arrived there to receive a plaque declaring him an honorary citizen of the town.
Top Budva official Marko Carevic also presented Djokovic with an Orthodox Christian icon in gratitude for helping preserve the Serbian people and the Serbian church in Montenegro.
Djokovic is adored in his native Serbia and among the Serbs in neighboring Montenegro, a small nation of some 620,000 people. Since he returned home, Djokovic was seen visiting churches and attending liturgies in both Serbia and Montenegro.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/3882c5eb13394276a92d659d2b020a45]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic in Montenegro after Aus. debacle]]></title>
      <guid>s6JW4KjQwCM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s6JW4KjQwCM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/s6JW4KjQwCM.mkv" length="5292022" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/s6JW4KjQwCM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363406

Despite relative calm in Ukraine's east, soldiers who have been defending against Russian encroachment are preparing for an escalation.
At the Novooleksandrivka outpost, the soldiers in the small garrison are wary as they keep watch over the landscape. 
Soldiers worry that a first strike could be in easter Ukraine, where pro-Russia separatists have been in control since 2014.
Soldier Vikor Beliekov wonders if an attack might come from the sea to the south.
Our navy is not enough to withstand heavy attack, he told the Associated Press, I think the coastline could be easily captured. Everyone thinks through Kharkiv or Donbass but it's a wrong point of view. If they decide to attack, they will do it from the sea.
Tensions have soared in recent weeks as Russia moved about 100,000 troops near the border with Ukraine.
NATO allies are bolstering their presence in the Baltics, and the U.S. has put 8,500 troops on alert.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/666fce0476b648a5a859b53ac8cd6dd2]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Ukrainian soldiers prepare for escalation]]></title>
      <guid>t5LgKd8WNZI</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t5LgKd8WNZI</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/t5LgKd8WNZI.mkv" length="4538053" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/t5LgKd8WNZI/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) FOR CLEAN VERSION SEE STORY NUMBER: 4363392

With its opening ceremony now just a week away, China has been using the Beijing Winter Olympics to promote winter sports, many of which are new to most Chinese, for fitness and business opportunities. 
The push has proved lifechanging for Li Wei. 
The tall, tanned 36-year-old farmer-turned ski coach works December to March at a resort in the Yanqing district, which will host skiing, luge and other sliding events for the Beijing Games.
Skiing boosted my income to another level, said Li, who charges 400 to 500 yuan ($60 to $80) per lesson — almost as much as his family earns in a week growing corn during warmer months. 
Many in Beijing have long enjoyed winter ice skating on canals and lakes. But now, young Chinese are expanding their aspirations from basketball, football and gymnastics to sports such as hockey and skiing.
The government and private companies have built ice rinks and ski runs. 
Public schools are adding skating and other winter sports. Parents are opening their wallets to pay for hockey teams and skating lessons. Villages near ski slopes are building inns to serve well-heeled tourists.
Wu Mengkai, 11, said hockey has turned him to being more extroverted and a very sunny person.
You can't be introverted when you play ice hockey, Wu said. You have to be brave enough to fight.
The Chinese capital has tightened anti-virus measures and ordered mass testing of some 2 million people in one district following outbreaks. Some families are barred from leaving their homes.
The Winter Games will take place without foreign tourists or ordinary spectators under China's zero tolerance strategy that aims to keep the virus out of the country. Athletes, reporters and officials are required to stay within areas that isolate them from general public.
Foreign sports brands see growth opportunities in China but are frustrated that marketing and business development are hampered by the anti-virus controls and ban on most foreigners from entering China.
That's kind of put a damper on things, said Jeffrey Potter, president of Proskatecorner Pte. Ltd., the China distributor of American hockey equipment maker True. 
If not for the virus, the marketing boost from the Olympics would have been bigger, really helping the economy and making hockey more popular, Potter said.
Despite the Games being off limits to ordinary spectators because of the pandemic, enthusiasm for winter sports remain high.
I want to be an ice hockey player in the future, said eight-year-old Guo Yuchen, who took up the sport at four and trains seven hours a week at a rink in Beijing. Then I can bring glory to my country.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/738ae9fb6d344cea8f0416b37957c75f]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Olympics give winter sports boost in China]]></title>
      <guid>v9pDwQSWndM</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v9pDwQSWndM</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/v9pDwQSWndM.mkv" length="4683846" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/v9pDwQSWndM/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) An oil slick off the coast of Thailand continued to expand Friday and was approaching beaches on the east coast, home to fragile coral and sea grass, officials said. 
The oil leak from an undersea hose at an offshore mooring point used to load tankers was stopped early Wednesday morning, but not before 140 to 375 barrels, or between about 22,000 and 60,000 liters (5,800 to 15,850 gallons), spilled into the Gulf of Thailand, according to Star Petroleum Refining, the operating company.
There are now two slicks, a small one about one square kilometer (less than half a square mile) that is closer to the coast and another that has broadened to 47 square kilometers (18 square miles) that is not far behind it, said Siam Lawawirojwong, director of the department that deals with disasters at Thailand's Geo-Informatics and Space Technology Development Agency. 
The Royal Thai Navy, which has been part of the cleanup and containment effort, said the main slick is expected to reach an area of coast including the Khao Lam Ya National Park by about 10 p.m. 
The park is home to a variety of seabirds and fish.
In preparation, floating booms were being deployed to try and trap the oil and contain it so that it can be collected from the surface and removed. 
Pornsri Sutthanarak, deputy director-general of the Marine and Coastal Resources Department, said Thursday that if the oil reaches the coast, it might also affect 59 acres of coral and 118 acres of sea grass, causing environmental damage that would take time to rehabilitate.
Initial estimates from Thailand's Pollution Control Department were that much more oil had leaked than reported by Star Petroleum Refining, and Siam said it was not possible at this juncture to say exactly how much was in the slicks. 
Speaking on the beach in preparation for clean up efforts Governor of Rayong Charnna Iamsaeng said the company that is responsible for this mistake must take full responsibility.
The leak occurred at about 9 p.m. local time Tuesday at a mooring station about 20 kilometers (12 miles) southeast of the Map Ta Phut Industrial Estate, south of Bangkok, Star Petroleum Refining said.
On Thursday the main slick covered 11.65 square kilometers (4.5 square miles) and Star Petroleum Refining said it had been spraying dispersants on the slick to try and clear it from the surface as it approaches Rayong province beaches. 
In all, four ships have been deployed to skim oil off of the sea's surface and another seven have been spraying the dispersants, the company said.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/1c6401f69f0e42b0b0c49c35a3f4411e]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Thailand prepares to clean up massive oil spill]]></title>
      <guid>w1EgyAFnveE</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w1EgyAFnveE</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/w1EgyAFnveE.mkv" length="7199972" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/w1EgyAFnveE/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description><![CDATA[(28 Jan 2022) The city of New York has given an emotional final salute to a rookie police officer gunned down with his partner a week ago. 
A funeral Mass for Jason Rivera was held Friday morning at St. Patrick's Cathedral. 
Mayor Eric Adams, who is a retired police captain, says he sees an echo of himself in the slain officer who had joined a department he had seen as flawed in hopes of improving it. 
The 22-year-old Rivera was recently married and barely into his second year on the force. 
He and Officer Wilbert Mora were fatally wounded when a gunman ambushed them in an apartment as they responded to a family dispute.
During the funeral service, New York City Police Commissioner Keechant Sewell posthumously promoted Rivera to the rank of Detective First Grade.

Find out more about AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/HowWeWork 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP_Archive 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/APArchives ​​
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/


You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/f60469fa81e340cca66546fd28b0c797]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[News & Politics]]></category>
      <title><![CDATA[Emotional final salute to slain NYPD officer]]></title>
      <guid>zK2TeWC6eG8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <source>https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w</source>
      <author>AP Archive</author>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zK2TeWC6eG8</link>
      <enclosure url="http://184.148.248.90:8080/UCHTK-2W11Vh1V4uwofOfR4w/zK2TeWC6eG8.mkv" length="11524539" type="video/x-matroska"/>
      <itunes:image href="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zK2TeWC6eG8/hqdefault.jpg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
